The morning chime has rung. I am Ayaka Yasumoto, attendance number 5 at Ebisu City Junior High School.
It's time for the Studer Gamers Club. It's time for the Studer Gamers Club.
This time, I'd like to play the third episode of the Soonest Day series.
It was difficult for me to say caw, and I tried to challenge myself, but I couldn't say caw,
So this time, I would like to play the game with a theme.
This is a new way to challenge horror films.
Okay, let's pull it out.
Here we go.
Store clerk! I would like to enjoy this game in the style of a store clerk.
Now I would like to play the third episode. Yes, so, welcome everyone.
This store will be a fashionable apparel store using used clothes and so on,
Sometimes, sometimes there are loud noises.
Sometimes there are loud noises in the store.
Please try not to be startled.
Yes, sir.
Oh!
This game is dangerous.
Morning Rap
He says, "I wish you all the best.
I'm sorry for your loss.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Let's be happy first
I guess this is it.
Episode 1
It's a little bit different from before.
The atmosphere is a little different...
Hmm...
I'm still in the mood for sales clerk stuff, but...
Oh...
It's almost time... it's almost time... welcome!
I'm sure you'll have a lot of fun today, so if you'd like, please buy some consar.
Thank you... we have a variety of products... and I'd be happy to help you.
It's called "Tsugumi" but I'm home.
I'm not home.
You're going upstairs?
Yes, I have some shopping to do today. I think I'll go straight home after shopping, so please be careful when you go home, too.
Well then, thank you very much. We look forward to seeing you again.
I'm kind of at work, and I'm getting hungry, and I'm kind of curious about something this evening, but...
I think I found a little prowler.
I found a suspicious person who shouldn't be in this restaurant.
Oh, it's starting to rain again.
It's raining harder and harder, and I don't think we'll get any more customers. Yes, so this is the third episode of, oh, you mean the third episode is still going on.
Well then, I'll be going on with today's episode.
I've been working here for about five years now.
Yes, my mother loves cakes.
Oh, I still met my mother.
I'm home.
You know, store clerks and these situations are already so different,
I can't be successful anymore. Mom, I'm going shopping. I'm coming straight home.
I'd like to have a conversation with you,
I'd like to play this game of "Chop Shop Clerk," which I'm afraid of.
I have an image of a chop store clerk who is a bit snide because he can't hurt you with his brain.
I'm sure he talks to you a lot like this.
Your mother recommends that you go home early.
Is something wrong with your mother?
I didn't seem out of the ordinary.
Like the food? Sure, if you're hungry.
She said we'll have a snack when we get back, which means something will probably happen to your mom after this.
It's the next day, isn't it?
It'll be different if it was Fukugawa
Looks like your father cooked dinner last night
I wonder what happened to your mother, as I recall
Mom's here
She's finally here.
It happened in the first episode.
Mom's here! She's finally here! Well, it happened in the first episode.
Oh! Mom's gone.
What's going on? Mother?
Hello, Mother.
Mom, what's going on?
Mom, are you preparing a snack? Is she preparing a snack? Good morning, sir.
Mom, do you have a snack for me? Is she preparing a snack for me?
I hope it's the same as usual.
But I don't think it's ever going to be the same again.
I don't know what's going to happen when you're gone.
I'm pretty sure this is going to be the point where she'll come back.
I'm looking forward to seeing what's going to happen in the future.
It's difficult to become a sales clerk while playing the game.
I thought it would be fun to be a store clerk.
I was a little excited, but it's difficult.
If it rains again, your clothes will be ruined!
Hmmm...
Ah!
I noticed something strange.
Hey, Mom.
Where did she go?
I miss her.
I miss her, I miss her, I miss her, I miss her, I miss being a mother, I miss eating her food.
Oh, Mom...
Oh, Mom!
There she is!
She found me, just now.
Mom! Mom!
Mom, you're wearing a T-shirt like a rock star.
Are you buying a T-shirt like a rock star or are you changing?
What's that?
Huh?
This... this... this... this... this... this...
Odd? He's saying something's wrong.
He's saying something.
I don't know what it's saying.
"Onzoromizo.
Oh, he's saying Tsugumi-bun.
I wonder if people who get really freaked out by this will still get all worked up and scared by this.
This one's coming right up.
Huh? Tsurumi?
Is Tsurumi walking with her father? Mom will be back soon.
Why would she go away without Tsurumi?
That's true. I wouldn't leave her behind.
I can't pick her up much.
It's just a matter of patience until your mom comes back.
Oh, it's raining again.
Oh, Dad?
It's starting to rain.
No, Dad, it's just a little flicker.
Are you okay? You're not going away, are you?
Okay, now I'm racing you!
It's peaceful.
Good, good, now you're competing with your father. Peace. Hey, Don!
Umi, I don't think that's a good idea right now.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh.
There's Mom.
I wonder what the story will be after this.
Oh, she's walking with almost... again.
I'm glad I called the police on your mom, because I'm worried about her, and I was wondering if you could put her on, even though your dad's at work and can't pick her up.
I see.
I'm sure you're worried about her too.
Hey, which one is it?
Thanks for your help.
Oh, the police.
What's that? The police?
Oh, no.
Wait, there's something going on with the police, too.
The fire... the fire... it's a good day.
It's my mom's day.
Wait, your mom's turning into Gori Matcha, isn't she?
I miss her too.
Oh, Dad.
Dad's taking mom's place, but don't worry.
You know, this game is starting to get a little surreal, don't you think?
What? What do you mean?
I'm your mom now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
She said we're gonna have to work on our girl talk.
It's tough.
You look good.
Oh, it's cute in a Tsugumi way, Dad.
I see. Don't get it, Dad.
Don't get carried away.
You're not my dad anymore.
Not your dad anymore?
Call me Mom.
What the hell are you talking about?
Okay, hold on.
Well, I guess you'll have to wait a minute.
I'm just a guy with a daughter.
Don't make any funny incidents.
Huh?
Oh, my God...
Well, but the police are also worried if Dad suddenly looks like this,
I wonder if they'd be a little worried if he suddenly changed his appearance.
Will it be a failure?
What's going to happen?
The next day? What? The title of this was "the next day," right? What does that have to do with anything? Next day next? What? This was titled "The Day After Next," right?
What does that have to do with anything? The next day.
Something changed. Does it matter?
What the hell is that?
Oh, Dad.
You're glowing.
Hey, Mom, I think I've discovered what it's like to be a woman.
Oh, yeah.
It's a little sensitive. So, I'm thinking about going into show business, but I've got eight more dads to go.
I'm afraid that if I'm cute, I'll be taken advantage of... and I'll have to talk to my daughter about it.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea to have a new job, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea to have a new job.
I'm not there yet.
Hello, Mawari-san.
I'm starting to end all my words with "koshi".
Oh, you've got some nerve, you son of a bitch. Wait a minute, you don't have to go that far.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Not a gun. No, you can't pull a gun on me.
Let me roll up your skirt a little bit. No, you don't want me to roll up your skirt.
I don't want to see it either.
You're going to allow me to flip this up, aren't you? Yes, just flip it up.
No, I don't think you should flip it.
Mm. Child, daughter, look.
Hmm?
Tracer, tracer.
Uh, hmm?
What are you doing?
Put that dirty thing away.
Mmm-hmm.
Oh, yeah, I cried.
En-en-en.
Dad, pull yourself together.
"En-en-en.
Are you smiling? Dad, are you...
Dad, are you laughing?
This isn't the kind of thing you do as a sales clerk or anything.
Dad, are you okay?
Next day, next day.
And here we go again.
I'm thinking back to the second episode, the second episode.
You know, with your brother...
Dad.
Challenge or I like water tea Challenge or I like water tea Challenge or I like water tea, Sukumizu-chan. I see.
Well, girls like to be afraid.
What? Suspicious person, Hiyori. I hear you, Tsugumi.
What? Ah, Tsugumi. Hmm? Your mother has hell-ears.
Huh? You don't think much of Dad, do you, Tsugumi?
That's surprising, because he was your father just yesterday.
I'd say, "You've got to be kidding me.
And here we go, gorimacho.
Papaguri. So it says "titch," right there. So it's not "Tsukumi" or something, it's "Chichi.
I'm talking to the state power.
I'm only here because I thought it was going to rain today.
I've been crying in the rain.
Oh, yeah, yeah, you got off?
Hmm?
What do you mean?
It's cold. Oh, well, that's good.
I'm glad I didn't get hit.
Hey, Choo-choo, let me ask you something.
This man is your father.
Isn't he?
Is he your mother? No?
What do you mean? No?
Well, which one is it? Is it your father? Is it the mother? No? What do you mean? No? What? Which one is it? Is it dad? Is it mom?
I don't know.
The person I thought was my father is my mother.
But she's someone else.
Uh-huh.
You don't know who this person is.
It's a difficult case for a child.
What do you mean, sir?
What do you mean?
Because you're a dad, and you're a first-round car driver, right? You're a father... He's a girl who woke up after her mother disappeared and he was taking her place.
He's a kidnapper.
How can I help you?
What?
What? Oh! Dad! Daddy, they've got you!
What's going to happen to my daughter?
What?
What kind of pervert does that with a kid?
Who's that? The pervert with the rub.
You're done.
What do you mean, this whole game?
What do you mean?
Earlier, you were wearing your sister's sailor suit.
And the father became a girl.
Is this a surreal game, or a horror game?
If you're a beginner, it's a hard game.
Is there something else?
I mean to move this out of the way again.
Now that pose.
You can see the beautiful lines of her body, though.
And that brings us to the third episode.
What's this?
Let's see...
What kind of feelings and games should I play with this game?
Should I experience it as a horror or is this a comedy?
That's all for SADA GAMERS CLUB. Thank you very much.